Loot Welcome to Rupees Like Share and
Subscribe Like that he got stock
shown on the screen that ICICI Lombard was
working with permission pressure yesterday high
security the kind of pressure the more the
button pressed the numbers were weak conversation
but it was saying well it died in the
stock is under pressure and this 1617
stop was doing 13020 management commentary
now see thousands of people share
about themselves whatever you add from here in the last one
pressure some more quotas will be applied for this
porn it will take
time new questions
are muted and that is why this piece is known
and the problem is
yes it is definitely that he said that he will give
Africa the highest impact of potato police
physical quarters if it will not have its impact then
it will definitely be seen helping one
but Rafi sahib will now keep its chart
if you just call it Kumar that you people
who is his award at this time as you
said it can be seen in the days of admission through many types of mediums
and the
way it is busy going on  There is a speculation that LIC's
IPO could fetch a lot now, so in a
way, the insurance paper
guarantee that is available in Lombard General Insurance is
not available in Life Insurance, but I personally believe that if there is a
glut of insurance paper
in the market, then there will be backlash from there,
so I think that at this time, we should widen it a bit
and tighten it a bit. If the next
quarterly results are better, then it can be seen there. At this
time, if someone
wants to take a position by adopting insurance mix, then I think SBI Life can prove to be a better and good option. Even in the morning, when fundamental issues were discussed, Maheshwari was going to ICICI Lombard, that is why at this time he also wanted to allocate space including a
plot, but if he says that, then also
betting on space by Life Insurance seems to be a
better option. Now tell me brother, is there a
proof instead of the way
we saw that in this, both the two
bars have become
width and you are
preparing to subscribe,
so I can cut from here.
Subscribe to the channel.
Advised to stay subscribed,
what happened to such loot on Vivo and you
people should pay attention in detail to the funeral,
extraordinary ashes etc. of Akshay Bank,
whose numbers are to be known tomorrow.